{
  "topic_id":"113",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Select the adverb in the sentence.\n Emily worked briefly on her report.",
      "choice": ["report", "briefly", "worked", "her"],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Select the adverb in the sentence.\n Darren accidentally deleted three hours of homework with one click.",
      "choice": ["deleted", "homework", "accidentally", "with"],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Select the adverb in the sentence. We went to the beach yesterday.",
      "choice": ["yesterday", "went", "beach", "We"],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Select the adverb in the sentence.\n The kayak was speeding wildly through the rapids.",
      "choice": ["through", "kayak", "was", "wildly"],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Select the adverb in the sentence.\n My brother always picks on me.",
      "choice": ["brother", "picks", "always", "on"],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Adverbs modify:",
      "choice": [
        "nouns",
        "nouns and pronouns",
        "only adjectives and verbs",
        "adjectives, verbs, and other adverbs"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "modify": "ቀይር"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Adverbs answer all of the following questions EXCEPT:",
      "choice": [
        "Where? When? How? To what extent?",
        "When? How often? How long?",
        "Where? When? How? How often? To what extent?",
        "How often? Who that be? How much? To what extent?"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "EXCEPT": "በስተቀር"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "The correct comparative form of the adverb 'quickly' is:",
      "choice": ["quicker", "quickest", "more quickly", "quicklier"],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "quick": "ፈጣን"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Complete the following sentence with the correct interrogative adverb:\n ________________ do birds fly south for the winter? (reason)",
      "choice": ["Why", "How", "Where", "When"],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "interrogative": "የሚጠይቅ"
        },
        {
          "fly": "መብረር"
        },
        {
          "winter": "ክረምት"
        },
        {
          "birds": "ወፎች"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Complete the following sentence with the correct adverb:\n The two brothers are ________________ talented in the performing arts.",
      "choice": ["as", "equally", "as equally", "no"],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        {
          "correct": "ትክክል"
        },
        {
          "brothers": "ወንድሞች"
        },
        {
          "talented": "ተሰጥኦ ያለው"
        },
        {
          "performing": "በማከናወን ላይ"
        },
        {
          "arts": "ጥበባት"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
